$(document).ready(function() {

const questions = [
    {
        question: "A dynamometer is used to measure...", 

        choices: {
            a: "the internal and outer dimensions of brake calipers", b: "the power and/or torque produced by an engine", c: "the horsepower generated by a car's window decals", d: "the heat emitted by a car's transmission"
        },

        answer: "b" 

    },

    {
        question: "Historically, car manufacturers have increased the horsepower of smaller displacement engines by using all of the following, EXCEPT:", 

        choices: {
            a: "nitrous oxide", b: "variable valve timing", c: "increasing compression and max RPM", d: "forced induction"
        },

        answer: "a"

    },

    {
        question: "In 2016, the fuel economy of all new cars in the U.S. rose to a record...", 

        choices: {
            a: "11.8 mpg", b: "19.3 mpg", c: "24.7 mpg", d: "29.8 mpg"
        },

        answer: "c"

    },

    {
        question: "Which of the following vehicles is NOT fully electric?", 

        choices: {
            a: "Tesla Model S", b: "Nissan Leaf", c: "Fisker Karma", d: "Jaguar I-PACE"
        },

        answer: "c"

    },

    {
        question: "The 2015 Dodge Challenger SRT Hellcat has more horsepower than which of the following cars?", 

        choices: {
            a: "2019 Ferrari PortoFino", b: "2018 Lamborghini Huracan", c: "2016 Honda Accord LX", d: "All of the above"
        },

        answer: "d"

    },

    {
        question: "VTEC is a feature of which of the following cars?", 

        choices: {
            a: "Ford Focus", b: "Acura RSX Type-S", c: "Toyota Camry", d: "Aston Martin Vanquish"
        },

        answer: "b"

    },

    {
        question: "In 1997, Car & Driver magazine named this vehicle the Best Handling Car at any price range:", 

        choices: {
            a: "BMW M3", b: "Chevrolet Corvette", c: "Porsche Boxster", d: "Ferrari F355"
        },

        answer: "a"

    },

    {
        question: "This recent technological innovation can be exploited by thieves to break into and/or steal certain cars", 

        choices: {
            a: "Blind spot detection", b: "Adaptive cruise control", c: "Remote keyless entry", d: "Lane departure technology"
        },

        answer: "c"

    },

    {
        question: "This sports car shares an engine with several Toyota models, including the Corolla and the Celica:", 

        choices: {
            a: "2018 Lexus LC500", b: "2002 Toyota Supra", c: "2004 Lotus Exige", d: "2008 Honda S2000"
        },

        answer: "c"

    },

    {
        question: "Italian-born Bruno Sacco is famous for his role as head designer of which car manufacturer from 1975-1999?", 

        choices: {
            a: "Alfa Romeo", b: "Ferrari", c: "Mercedes-Benz", d: "Fiat"
        },

        answer: "c"

    },

];

document.write(questions[0].question)

document.write(questions[0].answer)

});

